# Amar K Mahida

**PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY** 

Seasoned Manager - Marketing & Sales with demonstrated record of 10+ years of success in marketing, sales management and campaign development. Successful at overseeing all stages of initiatives, building positive relationships and promoting products with innovative and forward-thinking approaches. Well-versed in tracking market trends and capitalizing on important opportunities.

**EXPERIENCE** 

Constera Realty Pvt Ltd. - Manager - Sales & Marketing

Ahmedabad, India 09/2019 - Current

- To oversee Sales & Marketing aspects of day to day transaction & process
- Actualized strategies to continuously improve customer service, company or brand visibility and ongoing projects.
- Demonstrate products to customers, discuss features and redirected objections to capture sales.
- Responsible for Lead Generation, Corporate Presentation & all CRM related activities.
- Recorded client, tenant and sensitive information safely on ERP System, in compliance with confidentiality laws.
- Managed the marketing and sales team with project promotions by providing innovative ideas and sales techniques, for increasing sales exponentially.
- Active participation in Product launching & Expansion of business

Sobha Ltd - Deputy Manager - Direct & Channel Sales

GIFT City, Gandhinagar 01/2019 - 07/2019

- Responsible for Sales.
- Responsible for Lead Generation, Corporate Presentation.
- Maintaining the Quality of services for company's Goodwill and getting more bookings with the help of effective Market Research.
- Handle Broker's (Channel Partner) network and contribution through channel sales.
- Active Participation in Product Launching and Expansion of Business.
- Ensuring that the given target is achieved & make sure that the work done is according to the system implemented.

Ahmedabad india 382443 7874813474, mahida.amar@gmail.com

# CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Marketing and sales plan creation
- Business development
- Team leadership
- Sales strategies
- Marketing strategy
- Communications management
- Strategic decision making
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Marketing collateral
- Market and competitive analysis
- Presentations and proposals
- Marketing campaign management
- Established track record of exceptional sales results
- Offering sales support

#### **EDUCATION**

2011

Ahmedabad Institute of Management

Ahmedabad

**Master of Business** 

Administration: Marketing &

Sales *2009* 

**Bhavans' University** 

Ahmedabad

PG Diploma in IRPM: Industrial

Relations & Personnel Management 2008

J G College of Computer Applications

Ahmedabad

Bachelor of Computer Application

2005

**Divine Buds' School** 

Ahmedabad

# IL&FS Township & Urban Asset Ltd. - Assistant Sales Manager - Direct & Channel Sales

GIFT City, Gandhinagar 08/2018 - 12/2018

- Responsible for Sales.
- Responsible for Lead Generation, Corporate Presentation.
- Maintaining the Quality of services for company's Goodwill and getting more bookings with the help of effective Market Research.
- Handle Broker's (Channel Partner) network and contribution through channel sales.
- Conducting and taking active participation in Exhibitions and Promotions.

# **DBS Communities - Senior Manager - Sales & Marketing**

Ahmedabad 01/2016 - 08/2018

- Responsible for Sales, Collections & Marketing.
- Responsible for Lead Generation, conceptualizing marketing concept & timely rein enforcement of marketing campaigns through various marketing campaigns & channels
- Coordinating with Banks for payment collections & getting special attractive rates & offers exclusively for Group.
- Controlling of back office staff to update records and financial transactions.
- Proper coordination with team executives and various departments.
- Taking review of department on weekly basis.

#### WhooRealty Pvt Ltd - Regional Sales Manager

GIFT City, Gandhinagar 11/2014 - 12/2015

- Responsible for Sales & Marketing.
- Handle Broker's (Channel Partner) network and contribution through channel sales.
- Active Participation in Product Launching and Expansion of Business.
- Ensuring that the given target is achieved & make sure that the work done is according to the system implemented.

# Maruti Group - Manager - Sales & Marketing

Ahmedabad

08/2012 - 08/2014

- Responsible for Sales, Collections & Marketing.
- Looking after all the legal formalities regarding Booking Agreement, Agreement to Sale & Sale Deeds.
- Coordinating with Banks for payment collections & getting special attractive rates & offers exclusively for Maruti's client.

**HSC**: Science 2003 **Divine Buds' School**Ahmedabad

SSC

# Investors' Clinic Infratech Pvt Ltd - Senior Sales & Business Development Officer

Ahmedabad 06/2011 - 08/2012

- Responsible for Sales.
- Handling a team of Sales, Tele Marketing & Collections.
- Looking after the Entire Ahmedabad Branch & ensuring over all operation of the Branch.
- Ensuring that the given target is achieved & make sure that the work done is according to the system implemented

# PERSONAL DOSSIER

Date of Birth: 18th April 1987

Marital Status: Married

Language Known: Hindi, Gujarati, English.

Interests: Volleyball, Cricket, Music, Traveling & interacting with

people.

# **COMPUTER KNOWLEDGE**

**Database**: MS Access

Application software: MS Office & Visual Studio

Operating System: Windows 2000/XP